Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
- Box: 44, Folder: 6 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Incentives, Payrolls and Social Costs, Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
    By James F. Lincoln; Emerson P. Schmidt; Solomon Fabricant. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: An Audit of the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
    By Joseph L. Block. November 7, 1961. Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 7 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Look Into A Future of Opportunity, Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
    By Control Data Corporation. Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 8 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Employees' Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
    November 1, 1954. Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 9 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Share of Production Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    By Continental Paper Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Making Money With the Workers, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
    By S. Burton Heath. Reprinted from Future, September, 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 10 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Make Safety A Habit, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Supervisory Development Program: How To Instruct, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). January, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Supervisory Development Program: How To Instruct, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). January, 1953. Copy 2. No Cover. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Continental Oil Co. Supervisory Training Manual, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Grow With Conoco, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Policy Guide: Assistance To Transferred Employees, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Revised September 10, 1962 and April 1, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Personnel Procedures Guide, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). February 1, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Accidental Death, Dismemberment and Total Disability Insurance, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Included in Benefits Package envelop. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Disability Pay Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Long Term Disability Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Thrift Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Home and Hospital Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Home and Hospital Medical Expense Plan: Record of Medical Expenses, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Major Medical Expense Diary, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Conoco Scholarships, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Financial Aid to Education Program, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Continental Oil Co. Corporate Alumnus Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: The Oil and Gas Journal: Career opportunities in oil, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
    By Frank J. Gardner. November 9, 1964. Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 11 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.13 (1961:June 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.14 (1961:Nov. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.16 (1962:Jan. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.19 (1962:Feb. 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.21 (1962:Mar. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.2 (1962:May 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.42 (1963:Mar. 8). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.57 (1964:Mar. 31). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.66 (1964:May 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.61 (1964:June 4). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.1 (1964:June 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.2 (1964:June 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.3 (1964:June 11). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.4 (1964:June 12). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.5 (1964:June 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.5 (1964:June 15). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.6 (1964:June 16). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.7 (1964:June 17). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.8 (1964:June 18). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.9 (1964:June 19). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.10 (1964:June 22). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.11 (1964:June 23). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.12 (1964:June 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.13 (1964:June 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.14 (1964:June 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.15 (1964:June 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.16 (1964:July 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.17 (1964:July 9). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.18 (1964:July 10). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.19 (1964:July 13). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.20 (1964:July 14). Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.21 (1964:July 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.22 (1964:July 20). Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.23 (1964:July 30). Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.24 (1964:Aug. 6). Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.25 (1964:Aug. 24). Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Lake Charles Special Bulletin no.26 (1964:Sep. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 38: At Continental Oil Company's Lake Charles Refinery, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Max E. Stansbury. June 9, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: To All Continental Employees, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
    By Leonard F. McCollum. June 12, 1964. Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 12 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Conoco's Widening World, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Robert Sheehan. Reprinted from Time, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Your Stake in Press Relations, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: The CONOCOan: Continental Employees Newspaper, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). v.13:no.5 (1964:July/Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The CONOCOan: Continental Employees Newspaper, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). v.13:no.6 (1964:Sep./Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The CONOCOan: Continental Employees Newspaper, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). v.13:no.7 (1964:Dec./Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Supervisor's Kit, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). September, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Supervisor's Kit, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). December, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Tomorrow's News, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). v.3:no.2 (1965:Jan. 15). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.77 (1965:Feb. 26). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The CONOCOan: Continental Employees Newspaper: Reporter's Handbook, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Newsgram, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). no.78 (1965:Mar. 1). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Conoco's Approach to Employee Communications, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). Continental Oil Company and Subsidiary Companies. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: CONOCOLAND U.S.A. 1963, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Executives: Business in Politics, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Time. From Time, August 10, 1962. Includes correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Consol Story, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Leonard F. McCollum; A. W. Tarkington. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Make Your Career with CONOCO!, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 17: Employee Magazine Ideas: How Readers View the Employee Publication, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 18: CONOCO's Philosophy of Management, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). April 1, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: History of Continental Oil Company (Including Current Operations), Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 20: Management Organization, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). March, 1965. Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 13 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Conoco Safety Manual: make safety a habit, Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). July 1, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Continental Oil Company Safety Meeting Outlines for 1954, Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
    By Conoco (Continental Oil Company). December 1, 1953. Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 14 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Non-Salaried Employee's Retirement Fund of Continental Mills, Inc., Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
    By Continental Mills. December 28, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Continental Pathfinder, Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
    By Continental Mills. v.25:no.6 (1952:Sep.). Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 15 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A Proposal For A Career, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
    By Continental Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Information for the New Employee, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Bulletin, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
    By Continental Insurance Company. v.69:no.612 (1965:Aug.Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Hours of Work, Office Rules and Procedures, Dining and Recreational Facilities, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Effective Citizenship Program, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Voluntary Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: The Incentive Savings Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Group Hospital, Surgical and major Medical Expense Insurance, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Group Life Insurance and Survivor Income Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Individual Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: I have an Idea, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
    By Ray Gustafson. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Job Rating Check List, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Better Coverage Under Blue Cross, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
    By Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia. Included in Continental has great plans for you packet. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: A Real Major Medial Plan by Blue Cross and Blue Shield, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: Voluntary Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
    By Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company. Included in Continental has great plans for you packet. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Voluntary Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
    By Continental Insurance Company. Included in Continental has great plans for you packet. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 19: Comprehensive Health Care and Dental Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 20: Scholarship Plan for Higher Education, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 21: Individual Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 22: Comprehensive Health Care and Dental Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 23: Long Term Disability Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 24: A History of the Continental Insurance Company, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
    By Ann M. Kelchburg; Ronald G. Mullins. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: New Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 26: Job Title, Descriptions, and Coding, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 27: Pay in Lieu of Vacation on Termination of Employment, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Box: 44, Folder: 16 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Products and Services Directory, Publication (Box 44, Folder 16)
    By The Continental Group. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Carrying a Better Life Around The World, Publication (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Continental People, Publication (Box 44, Folder 16)
    By Continental Insurance Company. v.2:no.11 (1979:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Benefits, Publication (Box 44, Folder 16)
    By Continental Forest Inductries. November 11, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Operations Overview, Publication (Box 44, Folder 16)
    By Continental Forest Inductries. October 9, 1978. Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 17 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Careers at Continental, Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
    By Continental Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Corporate Profile, Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: UAC News, Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
    By Underwriters Adjusting Company. v.5:no.4 (1979:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: InScope, Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
    By INSCO. v.7:no.6 (1979:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: News, Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
    By AFCO. September, 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: News, Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
    By AFCO. Winter, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Survey of Employee Publications: Continental and Affiliates, Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
    By Continental Corporation. Blank Survey Instrument. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Performance Evaluation, Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
    By Continental Corporation. Blank Personnel form. Item is in English.
- Box: 44, Folder: 18 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Continental Employee Benefits Book, Publication (Box 44, Folder 18)